Preview of the Next Episode
In honor of the group's concept, nostalgic and sweet and sour like a coming-of-age novel
The group will be shooting a nostalgic and sweet and sour music video for their new song, "Grow Up Days," to be released on June 21 in Osaka.
So far, it's just a bunch of goofy food reports and too many free off-shoots, but we'll see how it turns out.
How will it turn out?
We came to Sumiyoshi-ku, Kita-machi, Osaka.
I didn't know there was such a place in Osaka!
Here it is!
This place is called "Handmade Kamishibai-Kan".
This is a place where we support the artists who create original picture-story shows and perform them everyday.
When is the last time you remember seeing a picture-story show?
The end of 6th grade.
Surprisingly recently
When was the last time you went to the library?
Not recently
Not recently.
I don't want to stop
Here.
Pee.
Oh, I just spotted it.
Let's take a slow pound.
Here.
Add some cuteness to your music video by looking at the camera as well as the off-shot!
Nominated members get to take delicious cuts like this one!
First Year Melo
Okay, here we go.
Ready
Yes, ma'am.
Sleepless nights
I got this.
That's good.
I like it. - I like it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Laughter
All right!
I was just, you know, the wind was blowing down a little bit and I went to get it myself.
Laughter
I went to get it.
That's a new style of fetching.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Hi, welcome.
The sweets are so expensive.
I love magrette!
I love Omori!
I've been eating these young doughnuts since I was a little girl.
I still eat them even now!
Crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
You all sound so good!
What is this?
If you eat it...
That's 300,000 yen.
I'm going to break my shoulder if I eat it.
So, the Muraho series, the only one I've never tried before.
The Muraho series, the only one of its kind I've never tried before, will have some.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Even if you didn't do anythingEven if you're not doing anything.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
You're alive.
It's fleeting, isn't it?
Since this is a place where you can learn about picture storytelling
I'd like to touch on the in-between
Oh!
Ayame Kawase, the oldest of the group, will be in charge of reading to the audience, and she will perform a picture-story show.
The remaining five of you will return to your childhood, in other words, have a nostalgic experience!
Gururuhoshi, hajimari hajimari!
Ah, Tanuki, wait, give me back my shoes!
I want to turn into a human girl.
This is a story of a girl and a tanuki.
A tanuki wants to buy something by transforming into a human.
The audience will join them in finding out what it is.
What exactly does Ponko-chan want to buy?
Let's see... something white and round and round.
White and round and round?
Well, what is it?
What do you think it is? The lady over there.
What's white and round and round?
String?
String!
Hey, sister.
The only thing I can think of is a cowlick.
No, it's not a cowboy!
Sister?
Soft serve ice cream! Wow, it's delicious!
You all want some, don't you?
I want some!
Good morning!
The Guru star is over!
It's so easy to understand, and it's so touching.
Great!
You've got great timing.
Will you be my Goddaughter?
I'm so happy!
Good morning!
It's out!
Did it come out? She's out!
It's my first time!
Please let me do it!
I've always wanted to do it!
Okay, let's do it!
Let's go!
Yes, yes!
ana
ni